(Stuart:)and I'm not even sure
you think of me as a friend.
(Stuart:)You have any idea
how that feels?
(Amy:)We're so sorry.
(Stuart:)I'm always the last one
anybody thinks of.
(Sheldon:)Well, no, that's not true.
(Sheldon:)I mean, sometimes
it's Koothrappali.
(Sheldon:)But we're not
supposed to say that 'cause
(Sheldon:)he's a minority.
(Stuart:)Bye.
(Sheldon:)Stuart, wait.
(Sheldon:)I do know what it feels like
to be left out.
(Bert:)I know how it feels, too.
(Sheldon:)All right, this is about me
and him; you're not part of it.
(Sheldon:)Stuart, perhaps we do
take you for granted,
(Sheldon:)and that is not acceptable.
(Sheldon:)Please know that you truly
are a valuable member
(Sheldon:)of our social group.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)You know, in fact,
I'd like to propose a toast.
(Sheldon:)To Stuart.
(Sheldon:)A fine man,
(Sheldon:)a good friend
and a wonderful guest.